I Have A Dream我有一個夢想。
I have a dream我有一個夢想。
A song to sing一首歌來唱
To help me cope幫助我度過難關
With anything隨你喜歡
If you see the wonderof a fairy tale
如果你看到童話故事的奇蹟
Of a fairy tale童話
You can take the futureinto your own hands
你可以掌握自己的未來。
Even if you fail, you should keep trying
即使你失敗了，你也應該繼續努力。
I believe in angels我相信天使。
Something good in everything I see我看到的每件事都有好處。
I believe in angels我相信天使
When I know the time is right for me當我知道時機成熟時
I'll cross the stream我會渡過溪流。
I have a dream我有一個夢想。
A fantasynovel
一本奇幻小說
To help me through幫助我度過
Reality現實
And my destination我的目的地
Makes it worth the while使它值得一試。
Pushing through the darkness推動著黑暗
Still another mile還有一英里。
I believe in angels我相信天使
Something good in everything I see我看到的每件事都有好的一面。
I believe in angels我相信天使。
When I know the time is right for me當我知道時機對我來說已經到了
I'll cross the stream我會越過小溪。
I have a dream我有一個夢想。
A song to sing一首歌來唱
To help me cope幫助我應對
With anything隨你喜歡
If you see the wonderof a fairy tale
如果你看到童話的奇蹟
Of a fairy tale童話
You can take the futureinto your own hands
你可以掌握自己的未來。
Even if you fail, you should keep trying
即使你失敗了，你也應該繼續嘗試。
I believe in angels我相信天使
Something good in everything I see我看到的每件事都有好的東西
I believe in angels我相信天使。
When I know the time is right for me當我知道是我的時候了
I'll cross the stream我會越過小溪。
I have a dream我有一個夢想。